/* array of questions */
const myQuestions = [{
            question: "Webahead has started with kav mashve at:",
            answers: {
                a: "Haifa in 2016",
                b: "Nazareth in 2017",
                c: "Haifa in 2019",
                d: "Nazareth in 2016 "},
                correctAnswer: "c"
            },
            {
                question: "Mahmoud and Mario have been mentoring the course together for almost:",
                answers: {
                    a: "one year",
                    b: "two years",
                    c: "three years",
                    d: "four years"
                },
                correctAnswer: "b"
            },
            {
                question: "Hussien is from?",
                answers: {
                    a: "Shefa-amer",
                    b: "Nazareth",
                    c: "Haifa",
                    d: "Sakhnin"
                },
                correctAnswer: "c"
            },
            {
                question: "Abed has finished a degree in?",
                answers: {
                    a: "Biology",
                    b: "Mathmatics",
                    c: "Law",
                    d: "Software engineering"
                },
                correctAnswer: "d"
            },
            {
                question: "Adan is ____ years old.",
                answers: {
                    a: "24",
                    b: "23",
                    c: "22",
                    d: "21"
                },
                correctAnswer: "a"
            },
            {
                question: "Her/his laptop is touch and she/he is living in Jaffa :",
                answers: {
                    a: "Nidaa",
                    b: "Elias",
                    c: "Hasan",
                    d: "Fadi"
                },
                correctAnswer: "c"
            },
            {
                question: "She/he has a degree in Mathmatics and has two little children?",
                answers: {
                    a: "Dana",
                    b: "Shireen",
                    c: "Nidaa",
                    d: "Adan"
                },
                correctAnswer: "c"
            },
            {
                question: "Elias is from?",
                answers: {
                    a: "Jdaide Maker",
                    b: "Haifaa",
                    c: "Jaffa",
                    d: "Jerusalem"
                },
                correctAnswer: "a"
            },
            {
                question: "Fadi is ____ years old.",
                answers: {
                    a: "25",
                    b: "26",
                    c: "27",
                    d: "28"
                },
                correctAnswer: "d"
            },
            {
                question: "Nour is from?",
                answers: {
                    a: "Bqeaa",
                    b: "Sakhnin",
                    c: "Um elfahem",
                    d: "Jatt"
                },
                correctAnswer: "b"
            }
        ];

        /** global variables */
        let count = 0;
        let numOfTries = 0;
        let isCorrect = false;

        let theQuestions = document.getElementById('questions'); // parent
        function startQuiz(){
            
        } 
        